

- +201030478962
- ahmed14massoud2021@gmail.com
- massoud.is-great.org
- Damas, Mit Ghamr, Egypt

EDUCATION

FrontEnd

Maaref website, Youtube 2020 - Now

Design

Youtube, Work Experience 2020 - Now

EXPERTISE

Python Script

Web Development

Design logo

SEO (SEARCH ENGINE OPTIMIZATION)

Montage

LANGUAGE

English

Arabic

AHMED MASSOUD

FrontEnd Developer

ABOUT ME

I'm Ahmed Massoud. I have been learning programming for a very long time in addition to school education. I love programming and writing code. I chose development as a field of study and I started with Front End and strive to reach a high position in this field maybe it require time, and I accept that.

Because of my hobby of writing commands and scripts, I learned Python and published some scripts.

And with my love for experimenting and discovering other fields, I learned montage and currently cooperated with a guran reader and started making this youtube video and I learned to make logos and actually worked on logos for some clients as a freelancer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Q 2020 - Now FrontEnd | Freelanc

> I worked on programming and developing websites for some clients, such as Portfolio, a website for the Qur'an Memorization House, and some freelance work tasks.

Apr 2024 - Now

Montage | Freelanc

I designed videos for the YouTube channel I cooperated with it. My mission was to transform the voice of the Qur'an reciter into a video with animated backgrounds and adding a subtitle for the recitation in an attractive way.

O 2020- Now

Logo designer | Freelanc

I have already designed some logos for some teams, such as the Byte Code team and others, and for many YouTube channels as freelance work

CODING

Html5

Css3

Bootstrab

Sass

Javascript

NodeJs

Php

My sql

Python

C++

WORK WITH

Byte Code

Programming Team . / CEO

Phone: +201508782161 Telegram: T.me/ByteCodeTeem Neural Kestrel / coder cipher

Programming Team / frontEnd Leader

Twitter: @Coder_Cipher

Email: CoderCipherDev@gmail.com